[PANTING]
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Leonard!
(Leonard(entering):)Hey, what's the matter?
(Sheldon:)Equations.
Someone's tampered with my equations.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
Look at the beta function
of quantum chromodynamics.
(Sheldon:)The sign's been changed.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)But doesn't that fix the problem
you've been having?
(Sheldon:)Are you insane?
Are you out of your mind?
Are you...? Hey, look, that fixes
the problem I've been having.
(Lesley:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)You did this?
(Lesley:)Yeah. I noticed it when I got up
to get water, so I fixed it.
Now you can show quarks are
asymptotically free at high energies.
(Lesley:)Pretty cool, huh?
"Cool"?
Listen, I gotta get to the lab.
(Lesley:)Thanks for a great night.
(Leonard:)Thank you. I'll see you at work.
(Sheldon:)- Hold on. Hold on.
- What?
- Who told you you could touch my board?
- No one.
(Sheldon:)I don't come into your house
and touch your board.
(Lesley:)There are no incorrect equations
on my board.